Darling, why give blood
when you could sell...
Plasma?
[laughing]
My name is Plasma, and I'm a 65 year old
woman inhabiting this gorgeous 24 year old's body.
My style is very 1950's Hollywood Glamour.
Ooooh, she's elegant.
Ooooooh
she's
royal.
[giggling]
I was raised listening to Julie Andrews,
Judy Garland, Barbera Streisand, all these musical theater giants.
And when I was very young, I realized that I wanted to be a performer.
And then when I learned that I could make
money being a performer,
bitch,
the game changed.
[everybody giggling]
[Plasma]: Diva, what's your name? [Hershii]: Hershii LaQuor-Jete.
[Plasma]: Girl...
You're going to have to say that one more time, a little bit slower.
I'm a great host.
I'm a great singer. I'm a comedian.
I love to connect with anyone and everyone in the room.
[Hershii]: Where were you from? [Plasma]: Well, I was born in Texas,
and then we moved to New York darling, New York!
What about you?
[Hershii]: She's a New York queen.
St Louis, Missouri, Atlanta, Los Angeles. I'm hometown for you.
[Plasma]: Okay! She got three names.
She got three homes! How about that?
[Hershii]: Period! This feels so surreal.
[Plasma]: Yeah.
I hate to say it, and it never has a good
connotation, but it's smaller than I expected.
[Hershii]: I expected it to be wider. [Plasma]: Wider?
[Hershii]: Yeah.
[Plasma]: I thought you said whiter, and I was like..
Well.
[both audibly laughing]
[lively and vibrant Mexican music playing]
Viva Mexico...
Ca..
brones!
Mwah!
[Geneva]: Mi nombre es Geneva Carr, or as everybody knows me, Geneva Broom Broom Carr.
Geneva Carr's drag style is very dramatic.
Escándalo, brillo, fantasía, and of course, a lot of Mexican spice.
[Geneva]: How are you, Monster? Hello!
[Plasma]: Oh, sorry, I hit you with the hat. I'm Plasma.
[Geneva]: Purpose. We just started, you're trying to kill me!
[Geneva]: She's a dancing queen. She's a diva.
This Mexican puts the
ASS
in
Tex-ASS,
and soon all over the world..
boom